Guide to the Clara Fraser Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Clara Fraser papers, 1923-1998; 3187-003; 20.61 cubic feet 22 boxes
  - Publicity and Press Files, 1969-1998; Series 5
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1986 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1987 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1988 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1989 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1990 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Clara Fraser death announcements, 1998 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Clara Fraser photographs, 1991 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Kathleen Merryman, Tacoma News Tribune, 1988 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Lisa Schnellinger, Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1989 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Kathleen Merryman, Tacoma News Tribune, 1988; 2 - 90 minute audiocassettes (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Seattle Central Community College student Franciose Sinet 2/26/1989, 2 - 90 minute audiocassettes (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Post-Intelligencer reporter Lisa Schnellinger 4/22/1989, 3 - 90 minute audiocassettes (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Clara Fraser interview with Paula Reynolds, University of Washington Daily 7/22/1989, 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Clara Fraser on KING radio re Russian artist guest Vassily Buchin 8/2/1990, 120 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Barbara Winslow interview of Clara Fraser 8/5/1991, 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/12)
    - 1st session with Jordana 8/30/1992, 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Interview of Clara 3/31/1993, 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/14)
    - End of interview with Don McGaffin 6/26/1997, 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/15)
  - Writings, 1963-1998; Series 6
    - Index of Clara's writings, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Writings, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Response to "Notes on leadership", approximately 1970-1975 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Woman as leader: double jeopardy on account of sex, 1972 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Which road to women's liberaton: discussion draft, 1970 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - How to end a commune: guaranteed tactics for absolute disruption, 1970 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Revolution, she wrote, 1995 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Revolution, she wrote -- correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Column edits, 1995 (Box-folder 3/39)
    - Column edits, 1996 (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Column edits, 1997 (Box-folder 3/41)
    - Clara's columns, 1976-1992 (Box-folder 3/42)
    - Clara's Freedom Socialist articles, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 3/43)
    - Responses to Clara's column, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 3/44)
    - Clara's column reprinted in other papers, 1995 (Box-folder 3/45)
    - Writings about Clara Fraser, 1978-1996 (Box-folder 3/46)
    - Radical Women publications by Clara Fraser, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 3/47)
    - Freedom Socialist Party publications by Clara Fraser, 1969-1988 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Women workers - sparkplugs of labor -- drafts, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Miscellaneous writings by Clara Fraser, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Crisis and leadership, 1996 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Speeches and Educational Programs, Series 7
    - Educational talks and speeches, 1946-1955 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Philosophy of Marxism: two talks, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Writings and speeches, Approximately 1950s-1960s (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Fallout shelters: wisdom or folly, 1962 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Speeches on women's liberation, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - The Saga of women and labor in the United States, 1971 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Fascism talk, 1971 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Civil liberties and social issues cases, 1972 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - 1973 and beyond: the road to revolution (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Political parties and tendencies of the U.S. left, 1977 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Portland talk, 1982 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Sexual politics in the 80s, 1982 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Shoreline Community College speech, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Central Washington University talk, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - International Women's Day forum, University of Washington, 1983 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - National Lawyers Guild Alternative Law Day, 1983 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Toast to Henry at victory party, 1983 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Pacific Lutheran University meeting, 1984 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Breaking the Barriers of Job Discrimination Conference, 1984 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Green River Community Collete, 1984 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - San Francisco speech, 1984 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - "Suing your boss" talk to Everett Unitarians, 1985 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - National Association of Social Workers, 1985 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Proposal to Marxist Scholars Conference, 1985 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Lecture for University of Washington course, Famous Trials in Washington History, 1986 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Proposal to Marxist Scholars Conference, 1987 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Power conference at University of Washington, 1988 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - Transcript of voir dire examination for jury duty, 1988 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - Gloria and Nina's birthday speech, 1988 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Kruschchev talk, 1988 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Leadership models and social change -- Kellog Foundation, 1988 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Parrallels and Intersection conference, Iowa City, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Women and the Law conference, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Using the power of class to combat racism and sexism, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1989 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - A Socialist view of the 60s and since, speech for Democratic Socialists of America, 1989 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - National Radical Women speech, 1990 (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Upheaval in the Soviet bloc -- its impact on women, 1990 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Welcome speech for Freedom Socialist Party national convention, 1993 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Speech notes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - State and revolution class, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 4/44)
    - History of materialism class, 1961 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Young Socialist Alliance basic economics class, 1962 (Box-folder 4/46)
    - The irregular movement of history, 1962 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Young Socialist Alliance course on dialectical materialism, 1964 (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Capital class, 1966 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Woman as leader, 1972 (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Sexuality, sexism and mental health, 1972 (Box-folder 4/51)
    - Men, women and war talk to veterans' awareness conference, 1972 (Box-folder 4/52)
    - Troskyism, Stalinism, Maoism, 1972 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - University of Washington women's studies course, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/54)
    - Prison reform talk to STOP, 1973 (Box-folder 4/55)
    - May Day, 1973 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - Sex-role stereotyping and channeling in the public schools, 1973 (Box-folder 4/57)
    - Race, nation, ethnicity: the minority liberation movements, 1973 (Box-folder 4/58)
    - Political economy of sex and race discrimination in America, 1973 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - Fashions in human relations, 1973 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - Tribute to Cannon, 1974 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - Forum on women and power, 1975 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Feminism and the Law conference, Denver, 1976 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Lecture on dialectical materialism to classes on the Marxist method, 1977 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Management prerogatives vs. workers' rights, 1981 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Inlandboatmen's Union talk, 1981 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Unitarian Feminist Alliance, 1982 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Clara Fraser. A Call to activism: reviving the tradition of the rebel lawyer. Keynote address to Women and the Law Conference, Oakland, California 3/31/89, 1989; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Forum at UCLA on Upheaval in the Soviet Bloc and Impact on Women 3/17/90, 1990; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Clara. Radical Women. Santa Monica 2/17/90, 1990; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Clara testimony Freeway Hall case 4/20/92, 1992; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/4)
    - International Women's Day, 1993; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Seattle Radical women International Women's Day 1995 event 3/11/95, VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Clara Fraser and Tamara Turner re: Gloria Martin for Gloria Martin memorial 12/17/95, 1995; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Gloria Martin memorial at Jefferson Community Center (original) 12/17/95, 1995; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Gloria Martin memorial at Jefferson Community Center 12/17/95, 1995; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/3)
    - April 13th "a happy announcement", Approximately 1970s-1980s; 60 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Mayday in Moscow with SUD & Adrienne, 1993; 60 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Parallels and Intersections Conference, Iowa -- Clara's workshop, 1989; 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Clara Fraser -- Radical Women conference, undated; 90 minute audiocassette (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Democratic Socialists of American talk and discussion (part 1 of 2), 1989; 2 -- 90 minute audiocassettes (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Democratic Socialists of American talk and discussion (part 2 of 2), 1989 (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Subject Files, 1961-1997; Series 8
    - The Exodus song (sheet music), 1961 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Nightclub Cantata, 1981 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Letters to the editor, 1979 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - The Group without a Name (Psychiatric Research Society) conference papers, 1972 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Requests for legal advice, 1972 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Prostitution, 1972 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - KING-TV, 1972 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Clara's UW parking card, 1972 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Gloria Martin case, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Legal Services meeting, 1972 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Sylvia Brown case, 1972 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - School for Community Action, 1972 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Petition re child support collection fees, 1972 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Marc's case, 1972 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Proposed city charter change in police practices, 1971 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Freedom Socialist (newspaper) correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Freedom Socialist index of key articles, 1982 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Freedom Socialist newspaper, 1994 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Freedom Socialist newspaper, 1995 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Freedom Socialist newspaper, 1996 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Freedom Socialist newspaper, 1997 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Freesom Socialist (newspaper) fund drive, 1994 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Freesom Socialist (newspaper) funnies, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Freedom Socialist column ideas, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Robert Crisman writings, 1988 (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Travel and Retreat Records, 1980-1994; Series 9
    - Travel checklists, approximately 1980-1990 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Camano Island retreat, 1982 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Alaska cruise, 1984 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Marrowstone Island retreat, 1986 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Indian Island nuclear weapons storage, 1986 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Port Angeles retreat correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Residence Inn, 1987 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Port Ludlow retreat, 1987 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - Whistler Mountain, 1988 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Smyth House, Vashon Island retreat, 1988 (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Sudden Valley, 1988 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - North Beach retreat, 1989 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Whidbey Island retreat, 1990 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - California trip, 1990 (Box-folder 5/45)
    - Canal House retreat, 1994 (Box-folder 5/46)
  - Job Records, 1954-1978; Series 10
    - Resume file, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 5/47)
    - Jobs, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 5/48)
    - Jobs, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 5/49)
    - Job applications, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 5/50)
    - Job applications rejected, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 5/51)
    - Photographs, approximately 1972-1975 (Box-folder 5/52)
    - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center (SOIC), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center (SOIC) Woman's Day program, 1970 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Nina Harding and Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1970 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center Council reorganization, 1970 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center staff career development, 1970 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Letter to Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center Council re personnel policies, 1970 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center employment discrimination case, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Marjorie Singer correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Martin Luther King Service Center, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - John Birch Society attacks on OEO, Black Panther Party, 1969 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Concentrated Employment Program job, 1972 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Concentrated Employment Program, Seattle Washington. Procedures for internal organization, 1973 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Concentrated Employment Program manual, approximately 1970-1973 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Concentrated Employment Program labor market analysis, 1973 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Manpower client services proposal draft, 1973 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Manpower client services proposal second draft, 1973 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - CEP V annual report (Concentrated Employment Program), 1973 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Concentrated Employment Program, 1973 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Gypsy manpower program proposal, 1973 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Consulting Job Records, 1971-1977; Series 11
    - City of Seattle sex discrimination workshop -- administrative, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - City of Seattle sex discrimination workshop -- materials, 1973 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - City of Seattle sex discrimination workshop -- evaluation forms, 1973 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - City of Seattle sex discrimination workshop -- report, 1973 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Veterans Action Program seminar, Yakima, 1972 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Community Resources Training Center for Corrections seminar, 1972 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Women's Divorce Co-op, Bellingham, training, 1972 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Washington State Office of Economic Opportunity, 1972 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - Sexuality, Crime and the Law training, 1972 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Washington State Human Rights Commission staff training -- administrative, 1972 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - Washington State Human Rights Commission staff training workshop 1, 1972 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - Washington State Human Rights Commission staff training workshop 2, 1973 (Box-folder 6/31)
    - Washington State Human Rights Commission staff training workshop 3, 1973 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Washington State Human Rights Commission staff training final evaluation, 1973 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Seattle Central Community College proposal, 1972 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Boeing proposal, 1972 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Headstart proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Environmental Health Project proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Northwest Social Systems, Inc. proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 6/38)
    - Economic Research and Development Corp. proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Teach-in, 1972 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Pierce County Library Staff Association, 1975-1977
      - Pierce County Library Staff Association, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 6/41)
      - Mediation, 1976 (Box-folder 6/42)
      - Proposed terms of settlement, 1976 (Box-folder 6/43)
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 6/44)
      - Los Angeles Public Library staffing and salaries, 1975 (Box-folder 6/45)
      - Personnel cuts, staffing, and recall, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/46)
      - Position paper on part-time employment at Seattle Public Library, 1976 (Box-folder 6/47)
      - Management's contract proposal, 1976 (Box-folder 6/48)
      - Proceedings, 1975 (Box-folder 6/49)
      - Negotiating session notes, 1975 (Box-folder 6/50)
      - Negotiation session minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 6/51)
      - Management memos, 1976 (Box-folder 6/52)
      - Negotiating team correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 6/53)
      - Dual seniority system question, 1976 (Box-folder 6/54)
      - Members' comments, 1975 (Box-folder 6/55)
      - Department of Labor and Industries representation case, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6/56)
      - Requests for information from management, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/57)
      - Statement to management, 1975 (Box-folder 6/58)
      - Comparison of management and Staff Association contracts, 1975 (Box-folder 6/59)
      - Cartoons, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/60)
      - Press clippings, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/61)
      - Background on libraries, 1975 (Box-folder 6/62)
      - Staff Association "Organizer" newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6/63)
      - Planning, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/64)
      - Salaries, 1976 (Box-folder 6/65)
      - Promotions and transitional adjustments, 1976 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Pierce County Libraries revenue history, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Remote access expenditures, 1975 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Employee salary and classification program, 1975 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Intermediate salary proposal, 1976 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Contract preamble, purpose, table of contents, 1975 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Contract drafts, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Final contract, 1976 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - 1977 negotiations (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light Employment Discrimination Case Records, Series 12
    - Pleadings, filings and decisions before Hearing Examiner, 1974-1982
      - Verified employment compLaints, Clara Fraser vs. City Light, 1974 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Verified employment compLaints, Daisy Jones et al. vs. City Light, 1974 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Claim for damages, 1975 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Amended verified employment compaints, Clara Fraser vs. City Light, 1975 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Amended verified employment compLaints, Daisy Jones et al. vs. City Light, 1975 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Motions and notices, Daisy JoneS et al. vs. City Light, 1975 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Case documents, 1977 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Case documents, 1978 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Case documents, 1979 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Interest on back pay, 1982 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Notes on legal arguments, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Settlement agreement, 1979 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Case documents January-June (part 1 of 3), 1980 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Case documents January-June (part 2 of 3), 1980 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Case documents January-June (part 3 of 3), 1980 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Complainant's exceptions to the Hearing Examiner's proposed findings of fact, conclusons of law and order of relief, 1980 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Decision of the Hearing Panel, 1980 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Case documents July-September, 1980 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Minutes and tape log, 1980 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - Exhibit list, 1980 (Box-folder 7/30)
      - Electrical trades trainees case, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - Memorandum of authorities 3/2/1979 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Motion to dismiss petition for declaratory ruling 3/3/1979 (Box-folder 7/33)
      - Hearing Examiner decision 6/20/1980 (Box-folder 7/34)
      - ACLU amicus brief, 1980 (Box-folder 7/35)
      - Our exceptions to Pasette, 1980 (Box-folder 7/36)
      - Panel's six questions, 1980 (Box-folder 7/37)
      - Proposed oral arguments to Panel 7/10/1980 (Box-folder 7/38)
      - Clara's notes on 7/10/1980 arguments (Box-folder 7/39)
      - Certiorari/declaratory judgment, 1980 (Box-folder 7/40)
      - Cloud's exceptions 7/3/1980 (Box-folder 7/41)
      - Hearing Panel decision 7/21/1980 (Box-folder 7/42)
      - Reconsideration proposals - drafts, 1980 (Box-folder 7/43)
      - Motion to reconsider 7/3/1980 (Box-folder 7/44)
      - Cloud's answer to reconsideration motion 7/29/1980 (Box-folder 7/45)
      - Panel denial of reconsideration 8/1/1980 (Box-folder 7/46)
    - Hearing Transcripts, 1980
      Note: missing vols 13,14,15,25 (as received from donor)
      - Transcript volume 1 1/14/1980 (Box-folder 7/47)
      - Transcript volume 2 1/15/1980 (Box-folder 7/48)
      - Transcript volume 3 1/16/1980 (Box-folder 7/49)
      - Transcript volume 4 1/17/1980 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Transcript volume 5 1/18/1980 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Transcript volume 6 1/21/1980 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Transcript volume 7 1/22/1980 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Transcript volume 8 1/23/1980 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Transcript volume 9 1/24/1980 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Transcript volume 10 1/25/1980 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Transcript volume 11 1/28/1980 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Transcript volume 12 1/29/1980 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Transcript volume 16 2/28/1980 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Transcript volume 17 2/29/1980 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Transcript volume 18 3/3/1980 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Transcript volume 19 3/4/1980 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Transcript volume 20 3/5/1980 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Transcript volume 21 3/6/1980 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Transcript volume 22 3/10/1980 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Transcript volume 23 4/15/1980 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Transcript volume 24 4/16/1980 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Transcript volume 26 4/18/1980 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Transcript volume 27 4/21/1980 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Transcript volume 28 4/22/1980 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Transcript volume 29 4/23/1980 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Transcript volume 30 4/24/1980 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Transcript volume 31 4/25/1980 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Transcript volume 32 4/28/1980 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Transcript volume 33 5/7/1980 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Transcript volume 34 5/8/1980 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Transcript volume 35 5/12/1980 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Transcript volume 36 5/13/1980 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Transcript volume 37 5/14/1980 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Transcript volume 38 5/15/1980 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Transcript volume 39 5/16/1980 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Transcript volume 40 5/20/1980 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Transcript volume 41 5/27/1980 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Transcript volume 42 6/9/1980 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Transcript volume 43 7/10/1980 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Transcript witness testimony index (part 1 of 2), 1980 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Transcript witness testimony index (part 2 of 2), 1980 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Audiotapes of Hearing Examiner Proceedings, 1980
      - Audiotapes 1/14/1980 - 2/27/1980, 63 audio cassettes (Box 20)
      - Audiotapes 2/27/1980 - 4/25/1980, 64 audio cassettes (Box 21)
      - Audiotapes 4/25/1980 - 7/10/1980, 47 audio cassettes (Box 22)
    - Hearing Examiner Exhibits, 1980
      - Exhibits 1-82, 1980 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Exhibits 83-187, 1980 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Exhibits 189-271, 1980 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Exhibits 276A-370, 1980 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Exhibits 377-498, 1980 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Exhibits 503-653, 1980 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Exhibits 655-661, 1980 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Exhibits 662-670, 1980 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Exhibits 671-691, 1980 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Transcript Excerpts, 1980
      - 2-SP AA advocacy integral to job, 1980 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - 12-SP Paramilitaristic management, 1980 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - 14-SP AA short-circuited Pilot Management Training, 1980 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - 15-SP CF never told of inadequate/untimely performance, 1980 (Box-folder 10/10)